

riley.roush@gmail.com 317-508-6955 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/riley-roush-436 746142

Portfolio: https://rroush0f.github.io/rrportfolio/ Graphic Design Work: https://www.tradingpaint s.com/profile/68675/Riley-Roush

Front End and Back End Web Developer who graduated from the Eleven Fifty Academy in December 2021. Also a Graphic Designer with over 12 years of experience designing virtual and real race cars for myself and customers all over the country. Achieved a Gold, Blue, and Red Badge in Web Development while attending Eleven Fifty Academy.

Professional Experience

Assistant to Project Manager Esterline Construction Inc, Plant City, Florida, United States | July 2017 - March 2020

- In charge of maintaining a safe jobsite and assisting in clean-up of left-over supplies.
- Leading a crew of workers to install windows onto apartments

Crew Member Eagle Creek Nursery Co, Indianapolis, Indiana | May 2013 - August 2016

- · Unloaded trucks and made sure plants were well taken care of
- Part of a landscaping crew that went to customer's houses

Education

Web Development Eleven Fifty Academy at Indianapolis | September 2021 - December 2021

Over 12 weeks I learned and became fluent in TypeScript, ReactJS, HTML, and CSS.

General Studies Ivy Tech Community College at Indianapolis | August 2015 - December 2016

Key Skills

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Social Media
- Photoshop
- Back-End and Front-End Developing